<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Presentation>
  <PresentationID>4371290</PresentationID>
  <Title>Garden Lab Philippines - Organic and skin care products suppliers</Title>
  <Description>At Garden Lab Philippines, we believe in high quality beauty and skin care products (organic oils) that harnesses the healing powers of pure, natural ingredients to deliver honest beauty products that produce real results and enhance your well-being. No additives, no funny business. Just 100% pure organic oils at affordable prices. Garden Lab’s products in Philippines are 100% pure and non-toxic. It is one of the most unique and natural smelling tea tree oil in the market. Hence our essential oil is one of the most therapeutically effective oils in the Philippines. We care about the quality our formulas, so we strive to use ethically-sourced, environmentally-friendly ingredients. The market is saturated with beauty products that can be questionably sourced or utilize unethical practices, but we want our customers to be able to shop with peace of mind knowing that our products are ethical and made with sustainable ingredients. We provide you with the flexibility to either pay upfront or on delivery.</Description>
  <CreatedDateTime>08/08/2020 01:54:11</CreatedDateTime>
  <ThumbnailURL>http://c.asstatic.com/images/4371290_637324484933202500-118_88.png</ThumbnailURL>
  <embed>&lt;object width="481" height="402" id="player"&gt;&lt;param name="movie" value="http://www.authorstream.com/player/player.swf?p=4371290_637324484933202500" /&gt;&lt;param name="allowfullscreen" value="true" /&gt;&lt;param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always"/&gt;&lt;embed src="http://www.authorstream.com/player/player.swf?p=4371290_637324484933202500" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowscriptaccess="always" allowfullscreen="true" width="481" height="402"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font size='2'&gt;Uploaded on authorSTREAM by &lt;a href="http://www.authorstream.com/User-Presentations/gardenlab/" target="_blank" title="More presentations by gardenlab on authorSTREAM"&gt;gardenlab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;</embed>
  <PresentationUrl>http://www.authorstream.com/presentation/gardenlab-4371290-garden-lab-philippines-organic-skin-care-products-suppliers</PresentationUrl>
  <PresentationViews>174</PresentationViews>
  <Category>Others/ Misc</Category>
  <Tags>Apple Seed Oil,Organic oil,</Tags>
</Presentation>